// import shuffleArray from "../helpers/shuffleArray.js";
// import { getRandomItem } from "../helpers/shuffleAnswer.js";

export const ScarlettJohanssonQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "In which movie does Scarlett Johansson play the character Black Widow?",
    options: ["Avengers: Endgame", "Lucy", "Her", "The Prestige"],
    correctAnswer: "Avengers: Endgame",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of Scarlett Johansson's character in *Lost in Translation*?",
    options: ["Charlotte", "Anna", "Samantha", "Lucy"],
    correctAnswer: "Charlotte",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Marriage Story*, what is Scarlett Johansson's character's profession?",
    options: ["Actress", "Writer", "Lawyer", "Dancer"],
    correctAnswer: "Actress",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie features Scarlett Johansson as a woman with enhanced brain capacity?",
    options: ["Lucy", "Under the Skin", "Ghost in the Shell", "Don Jon"],
    correctAnswer: "Lucy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which animated movie does Scarlett Johansson voice a character named Ash?",
    options: ["Sing", "Zootopia", "The Jungle Book", "Finding Dory"],
    correctAnswer: "Sing",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which film stars Scarlett Johansson as an AI system named Samantha?",
    options: ["Her", "Lucy", "Ghost in the Shell", "Under the Skin"],
    correctAnswer: "Her",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *The Prestige*, what is the role of Scarlett Johansson's character?",
    options: [
      "Magician's assistant",
      "Journalist",
      "Detective",
      "Stage actress",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Magician's assistant",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which movie does Scarlett Johansson play a character called Major, a cyborg soldier?",
    options: ["Ghost in the Shell", "Lucy", "The Avengers", "Under the Skin"],
    correctAnswer: "Ghost in the Shell",
  },
  {
    question: "Which movie features Scarlett Johansson as a seductive alien?",
    options: ["Under the Skin", "Lucy", "The Island", "Don Jon"],
    correctAnswer: "Under the Skin",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *The Avengers*, what is Scarlett Johansson's character's real name?",
    options: [
      "Natasha Romanoff",
      "Wanda Maximoff",
      "Maria Hill",
      "Carol Danvers",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Natasha Romanoff",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Jojo Rabbit*, what is Scarlett Johansson's character's relationship to Jojo?",
    options: ["His mother", "His teacher", "His aunt", "His sister"],
    correctAnswer: "His mother",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie stars Scarlett Johansson and Adam Driver as a couple going through a divorce?",
    options: ["Marriage Story", "Under the Skin", "Lucy", "The Nanny Diaries"],
    correctAnswer: "Marriage Story",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Vicky Cristina Barcelona*, which character does Scarlett Johansson play?",
    options: ["Cristina", "Vicky", "Maria", "Isabel"],
    correctAnswer: "Cristina",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie features Scarlett Johansson as a nanny working for a wealthy family?",
    options: ["The Nanny Diaries", "Marriage Story", "Don Jon", "The Island"],
    correctAnswer: "The Nanny Diaries",
  },
  {
    question: "In *The Island*, what is Scarlett Johansson’s character's name?",
    options: ["Jordan", "Evelyn", "Natasha", "Lucy"],
    correctAnswer: "Jordan",
  },
  {
    question: "In *Chef*, what is Scarlett Johansson's role?",
    options: ["Restaurant hostess", "Chef", "Food critic", "Waitress"],
    correctAnswer: "Restaurant hostess",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Don Jon*, what is the name of Scarlett Johansson's character?",
    options: ["Barbara", "Lucy", "Charlotte", "Cristina"],
    correctAnswer: "Barbara",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which movie does Scarlett Johansson play a woman in a dystopian future who tries to escape a medical facility?",
    options: ["The Island", "Lucy", "Ghost in the Shell", "Her"],
    correctAnswer: "The Island",
  },
  {
    question: "In *The Horse Whisperer*, who does Scarlett Johansson play?",
    options: [
      "A teenage girl recovering from an accident",
      "A horse trainer",
      "A journalist",
      "A ranch owner",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A teenage girl recovering from an accident",
  },
  {
    question: "In which movie does Scarlett Johansson voice Kaa, the snake?",
    options: ["The Jungle Book", "Sing", "Zootopia", "Finding Nemo"],
    correctAnswer: "The Jungle Book",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie features Scarlett Johansson as a journalist who works with magicians?",
    options: ["The Prestige", "The Other Boleyn Girl", "Lucy", "Iron Man 2"],
    correctAnswer: "The Prestige",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Iron Man 2*, what is the alias Scarlett Johansson's character uses?",
    options: ["Natalie Rushman", "Pepper Potts", "Maria Hill", "Sharon Carter"],
    correctAnswer: "Natalie Rushman",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie stars Scarlett Johansson as an actress struggling with fame in Tokyo?",
    options: ["Lost in Translation", "Lucy", "Under the Skin", "Her"],
    correctAnswer: "Lost in Translation",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which movie does Scarlett Johansson play a 1940s femme fatale?",
    options: [
      "The Black Dahlia",
      "The Other Boleyn Girl",
      "Match Point",
      "The Prestige",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Black Dahlia",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Match Point*, what sport plays a significant role in the story?",
    options: ["Tennis", "Golf", "Soccer", "Basketball"],
    correctAnswer: "Tennis",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie features Scarlett Johansson as an alien who preys on humans in Scotland?",
    options: ["Under the Skin", "Lucy", "The Island", "Her"],
    correctAnswer: "Under the Skin",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which movie does Scarlett Johansson's character work in a supermarket while pursuing an art career?",
    options: ["Ghost World", "Lost in Translation", "Match Point", "Her"],
    correctAnswer: "Ghost World",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie features Scarlett Johansson as the love interest of an art gallery owner?",
    options: ["A Good Woman", "Scoop", "Iron Man 2", "Don Jon"],
    correctAnswer: "A Good Woman",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Sing 2*, what type of animal is Scarlett Johansson's character Ash?",
    options: ["Porcupine", "Elephant", "Pig", "Dog"],
    correctAnswer: "Porcupine",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Rough Night*, what event are Scarlett Johansson and her friends celebrating?",
    options: [
      "A bachelorette party",
      "A graduation",
      "A promotion",
      "A wedding",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A bachelorette party",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie stars Scarlett Johansson as a woman falling in love with an artificial intelligence system?",
    options: ["Her", "Ghost in the Shell", "Lucy", "Under the Skin"],
    correctAnswer: "Her",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *The Other Boleyn Girl*, who does Scarlett Johansson portray?",
    options: [
      "Mary Boleyn",
      "Anne Boleyn",
      "Catherine of Aragon",
      "Elizabeth I",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Mary Boleyn",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie features Scarlett Johansson in a love triangle with two friends?",
    options: [
      "Vicky Cristina Barcelona",
      "Match Point",
      "The Prestige",
      "A Good Woman",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Vicky Cristina Barcelona",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *The Avengers*, what is the name of the team Scarlett Johansson's character is a part of?",
    options: [
      "The Avengers",
      "The X-Men",
      "The Fantastic Four",
      "The Justice League",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Avengers",
  },
  {
    question: "In *We Bought a Zoo*, who plays Scarlett Johansson's co-star?",
    options: [
      "Matt Damon",
      "Brad Pitt",
      "Robert Downey Jr.",
      "Chris Hemsworth",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Matt Damon",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie features Scarlett Johansson as a young woman whose family moves into a run-down zoo?",
    options: [
      "We Bought a Zoo",
      "Marriage Story",
      "The Nanny Diaries",
      "The Island",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "We Bought a Zoo",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Scoop*, who does Scarlett Johansson's character team up with to investigate a murder?",
    options: ["A magician", "A journalist", "A lawyer", "A detective"],
    correctAnswer: "A magician",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which movie does Scarlett Johansson play a character with superhuman abilities after a drug is absorbed into her body?",
    options: ["Lucy", "Under the Skin", "Ghost in the Shell", "The Island"],
    correctAnswer: "Lucy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Hail, Caesar!*, what is Scarlett Johansson’s character's profession?",
    options: ["Actress", "Detective", "Writer", "Nurse"],
    correctAnswer: "Actress",
  },
  {
    question: "In *The Spirit*, what is Scarlett Johansson's character's name?",
    options: ["Silken Floss", "Nancy Callahan", "Jordan Two Delta", "Lucy"],
    correctAnswer: "Silken Floss",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which film stars Scarlett Johansson as a college student working at a camp?",
    options: [
      "The Horse Whisperer",
      "Home Alone 3",
      "Ghost World",
      "The Nanny Diaries",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Horse Whisperer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *The Avengers: Age of Ultron*, what does Black Widow use to calm down the Hulk?",
    options: ["A lullaby", "A drug", "A weapon", "A secret code"],
    correctAnswer: "A lullaby",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which movie does Scarlett Johansson play a woman who hires an escort service?",
    options: [
      "Don Jon",
      "Vicky Cristina Barcelona",
      "Lost in Translation",
      "Match Point",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Don Jon",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie features Scarlett Johansson as the Black Widow, a former Russian spy turned superhero?",
    options: ["Black Widow", "Lucy", "Ghost in the Shell", "The Prestige"],
    correctAnswer: "Black Widow",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *In Good Company*, what is Scarlett Johansson's relationship to Dennis Quaid's character?",
    options: ["His daughter", "His wife", "His sister", "His boss"],
    correctAnswer: "His daughter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie stars Scarlett Johansson as a journalist who receives a tip from a ghost?",
    options: ["Scoop", "The Prestige", "Lucy", "Match Point"],
    correctAnswer: "Scoop",
  },
];

export default ScarlettJohanssonQuestions;
